{
    "subject": "resource/Geoffrey_Rhodes_Bromet",
    "predicate": "ontology/militaryRank",
    "object": "resource/Air_vice-marshal",
    "human_readable": "Geoffrey Rhodes Bromet's military rank is Air vice-marshal.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9379124045372009,
            "question": "What is Geoffrey Rhodes Bromet's military rank?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8927115797996521,
            "question": "Is Geoffrey Rhodes Bromet a high-ranking military officer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.811247706413269,
            "question": "Are there different branches within the military that utilize the rank of Air vice-marshal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7819142937660217,
            "question": "What does the rank of Air vice-marshal signify in the military hierarchy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7251906394958496,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of other military ranks similar to Air vice-marshal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7190032601356506,
            "question": "How does the rank of Air vice-marshal compare to other senior military ranks?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6738122701644897,
            "question": "Are there specific criteria for achieving the rank of Air vice-marshal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6420833468437195,
            "question": "What are the responsibilities typically associated with the rank of Air vice-marshal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5674839615821838,
            "question": "What historical context surrounds the introduction of the rank of Air vice-marshal?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5587336421012878,
            "question": "Can you explain the significance of the term 'vice-marshal' in military terminology?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Geoffrey Rhodes Bromet's military rank is Air vice-marshal.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4346_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What historical context surrounds the introduction of the rank of Air vice-marshal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4346_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the responsibilities typically associated with the rank of Air vice-marshal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4346_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there specific criteria for achieving the rank of Air vice-marshal?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4346_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4346_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4346_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4346_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4346_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4346_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4346_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4346_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4346_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4346_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4346_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports the statement that Geoffrey Rhodes Bromet held the military rank of Air Vice Marshal, as explicitly stated in the text for \"7.txt\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}